The sales order agent and the payables
agent already available in many
countries. They can help your
organization speed up sales and accounts
payable. And getting started couldn't be
easier. To begin, you'll need to create
a shared mailbox that you and your
colleagues can use for sending a few
test emails.
In the Microsoft 365 administration
portal, open the Teams and Groups menu,
then select shared mailboxes. Next,
choose add a shared mailbox. Then
provide a name and email address for it.
Save your changes and give it a moment
for the mailbox to be created. If you're
testing this with colleagues, you can
also add them as members so they have
access to your shared mailbox is now
ready. Let's switch over to Outlook and
connect it to your account. Here
[Music]
you can see your own email account, most
likely already busy with plenty of
messages.
Now, let's go ahead and link the shared
mailbox you've just created.
Simply type the name of the account and
follow a few straightforward steps in
the wizard to finish the setup. You can
now see all the emails arriving in this
shared mailbox right alongside your own
in Outlook. Let's now switch over to
Business Central and activate the sales
order agent to start monitoring the
shared mailbox for requests for sales
quotes.
[Music]
Go through the email account creation
wizard. Choose Microsoft 365 account
type. While you can also use your own
account if you prefer, a dedicated
shared mailbox helps ensure the agent
isn't cluttered with irrelevant emails.
Now add the name and email address of
the mailbox you have prepared. Once the
account is selected, the agent activates
automatically. You just need to click
update to confirm. That's all. Your
agent is active and listening for emails
like your most attentive sales team
member. Let's give the agent something
to get busy with. Create an email using
your own mailbox detailing some items,
quantities, delivery dates, and so on,
and send it to the shared mailbox we've
just created.
And here it is. The email has landed
here.
Switching back to Business Central,
you'll see the agent has already picked
up the email and created a task for you
to review it. Because the email is
coming from you, you're probably not set
up as a contact in your own business
central environment. But don't worry,
adding any sender as a contact is quick
and easy. Simply review the details and
confirm to create the new contact. You
can now confirm for the agent to go
ahead and create a sales quote from this
email.
Give the agent a little time to read
through the details, find the items, and
fill out the quote. And here you go. The
quote is created without you having to
painstakingly search for and type in all
that information. If you ever need to
find your email accounts, just head to
the email accounts page. Here you can
register new accounts. For example, if
you decide to create a shared mailbox to
use with your customers or remove any
accounts you no longer need.
Ask your colleagues to challenge the
sales order agent with some of their own
test requests for quotes.
See how it handles their tasks and
discover the difference it can make for
your business.